<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="gpu_1">
        <item>AMD Radeon RX 5700</item>
        <item>$599.94</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 8GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1465MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1725MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 6\n
            - Length: 270mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n Great gaming experiences are created
            by bending the rules. The AMD Radeon™ RX 5700
            Series GPUs defy conventions with an all-new 7nm
            process infused with RDNA architecture that is specifically tuned for
            the perfect 1440p gaming experience. More efficient processing power handles
            advanced 3D effects with ease, and 8GB of high-speed GDDR6 VRAM provides ample storage for the
            detailed textures, meshes, and effects of modern games. Industry-leading software and
            frequent driver upgrades push the experience even further, enabling overclocking,
            gameplay recording, and more.\n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gpu_2">
        <item>Nvidia GeForce RTX 2080 Ti</item>
        <item>$2149.95</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>"\n - Memory Size: 11GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1366MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1545MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 270mm\n
            - Display Ports: 2 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n Whether you\'re a PC gamer who has been waiting in the wings for a more powerful
            graphics card or you truly believe in Nvidia\'s vision of a ray traced future, the
            Nvidia RTX 2080 Ti is the new top dog in the world of graphics cards and a sound
            investment for you.\n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gpu_3">
        <item>AMD Radeon RX 5600 XT</item>
        <item>$573.89</item>
        <item>3.5</item>
        <item>"\n - Memory Size: 6GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1556MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1620MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 240mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n Armed with the newest and most advanced 7nm AMD RDNA architecture,
            PowerColor RX 5600 XT Red Dragon brings great performance with a dual 100mm fan and
            5x6F copper heatpipes. It features optimized performance for better visuals such as
            volumetric lighting, motion blurring effects, depth of field, and multi-level cache
            hierarchy for reduced latency and a highly responsive gaming experience. PowerColor
            RX 5600 XT Red Dragon is the excellent graphics card for 1080p users.\n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gpu_4">
        <item>Nvidia GeForce RTX 2070 Super</item>
        <item>$1049.00</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 8GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: N/A\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1785MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 289mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n In terms of value, the 2070 Super is a great option for people looking to
            build a high-end gaming PC. It places at the top of the charts for the FPS per
            unit of money spent on a complete PC. If you\'re only looking at the graphics card,
            however, the RTX cards—and really any high-end GPU—look far less enticing. Just
            remember that value means many things, and even a free GTX 650 probably won\'t get
            much attention from anyone looking to play the latest games. \n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="gpu_5">
        <item>Nvidia GeForce GTX 1660 Super</item>
        <item>$499.00</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 6GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1785MHz \n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1830MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 225mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n If you\'re on the market for the best graphics card for 1080p gaming,
            you\'re going to want the Nvidia GeForce GTX 1660 Super. The original GTX 1660
            was already the best entry-level graphics card, and Nvidia basically made it better
            in every single way. The Nvidia Super series has been kind of hit and miss – with
            the RTX 2080 being a notable flop – but we can\'t recommend the GTX 1660 Super
            enough. \n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gpu_6">
        <item>Nvidia GT 1030</item>
        <item>$155.25</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 2GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1252MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1506MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 2\n
            - Length: 150mm\n
            - Display Ports: None \n\n</item>
        <item>\n Accelerate your entire PC experience with the fast, powerful
            NVIDIA® GeForce® GT 1030 graphics card. Its award-winning NVIDIA Pascal™
            architecture, powerful graphics engine, and state-of-the-art technologies
            give you the performance upgrade you need to drive today’s most demanding
            PC applications. \n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gpu_7">
        <item>Radeon RX 570</item>
        <item>$240.35</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 4GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: Not Specified\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1250MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 5\n
            - Length: 255mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n It is based on AMD\'s latest GCN 4 architecture designed for GloFo
            14nm FinFET that delivers premium VR capability, increased level of performance,
            smooth VR, seamless support for next-gen gaming monitors and CPU-free game streaming
            or recording. AMD FreeSync™ technology puts an end to choppy gameplay and broken
            frames with fluid, artifact-free, performance at virtually any framerate.
            A power-saving feature that dynamically regulates frame rate based on your in-game
            movements. Radeon™ Chill can improve power efficiency and can lower temperatures
            for supported products and games when enabled through Radeon™ Settings. \n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gpu_8">
        <item>Radeon RX 5500 XT</item>
        <item>$424.35</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 8GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1607MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1845MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 233mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n The AMD Radeon RX 5500 GPU powers high fidelity gaming for immersive action,
            bringing realism to life. High-performance RDNA architecture was engineered to greatly
            enhance features like Radeon Image Sharpening, FidelityFX, and premium VR technologies
            for maximum performance and beautiful gaming experiences. Radeon RX 5500 XT features
            new compute units, new instructions better suited for visual effects, and multi-level
            cache hierarchy for greatly reduced latency and highly responsive gaming.
            High-performance RDNA architecture was engineered to greatly enhance features like
            Radeon Image Sharpening, FidelityFX, and VR technologies3 for maximum performance
            and jaw-dropping gaming experiences. Get the competitive advantage with dramatically
            reduced input lag with Radeon Anti-Lag, get stutter-free, tear-free gaming with AMD
            Radeon FreeSync1 technology, and the latest Radeon Software for incredibly responsive
            and insanely immersive gameplay. \n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gpu_9">
        <item>Nvidia GeForce GTX 1650</item>
        <item>$343.85</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 4GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1515MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: 1785MHz\n
            - Max Displays: 3\n
            - Length: 200mm\n
            - Display Ports: 1 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n The GeForce® GTX 1650 is built with the breakthrough graphics
            performance of the award-winning NVIDIA Turing™ architecture. Broadcast your
            gameplay with the GTX 1650\'s dedicated hardware encoder that is optimized for
            Open Broadcaster Software (OBS). GeForce Experience lets you capture and share
            videos, screenshots, and livestreams with friends, keep GeForce drivers up to
            date, and easily optimize your in-game settings. Space-grade lubricant brings
            the durability of dual ball bearings to quieter sleeve bearing designs. IP5X dust
            resistance offers protection from particle ingress for better durability. Auto-Extreme
            Technology uses automation to enhance reliability. A protective backplate secures
            components during transportation and installation. TUF Compatibility Testing ensures
            TUF Gaming and TUF Gaming alliance components work together flawlessly. 144-Hour
            Validation Program puts cards through a series of stringent tests to ensure
            compatibility with the latest games. Tweak II provides intuitive performance tweaking,
            thermal controls, and system monitoring\n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="gpu_10">
        <item>Nvidia GeForce RTX 2070</item>
        <item>$808.99</item>
        <item>4.5</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Size: 8GB\n
            - Base Clock Speed: 1620MHz\n
            - Boost Clock Speed: Not Specified\n
            - Max Displays: 4\n
            - Length: 264mm\n
            - Display Ports: 3 \n\n</item>
        <item>\n The Nvidia GeForce RTX 2070 Founders Edition packs futuristic hardware
            for ray tracing and AI-enhanced graphics, but it\'s also faster than the competition
            in traditional games. Nvidia\'s design is gorgeous, but similar performance can be
            achieved with lower-priced RTX 2070 graphics cards. The RTX 2070 Founder’s Edition
            is currently as close to a “value” proposition as you’re going to find with a
            Turing-based card. If you’re using a 1440p monitor and looking for a future-proof GPU,
            this card is a semi-affordable option with great looks and great performance. Still,
            you should wait for partner cards to drop in the future, as they should offer equivalent
            performance at a lower price.\n\n\n </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>