<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ram_1">
        <item>G.Skill Trident Z RGB</item>
        <item>$204.94</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB)\n
            - Memory Speed: 3200Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n Featuring a completely exposed light bar with vibrant RGB LEDs, merged with
            the award-winning Trident Z heatspreader designed, and constructed with the highest
            quality components, the Trident Z RGB DDR4 memory kit combines the most vivid RGB
            lighting with uncompromised performance. The uncovered light bar is designed for visual
            gratification in full RGB. The default lighting sports a fluid full spectrum rainbow
            wave. Downloadable software allows expanded effect and color customizations to the
            memory modules. Color match your build and rethink the possibilities with RGB. Each
            memory kit contains specially screened ICs through G.SKILL\'s unparalleled selection
            process and a custom engineered ten-layer PCB offering maximum signal stability; and
            every single kit is rigorously tested for reliability, compatibility, and performance
            across a wide range of motherboards. \n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_2">
        <item>Corsair Vengeance LPX Series</item>
        <item>$124.00</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 8GB (2 x 4GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 2666Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n Vengeance LPX memory is designed for high-performance overclocking. The
            heatspreader is made of pure aluminum for faster heat dissipation, and the
            eight-layer PCB helps manage heat and provides superior overclocking headroom.
            Each IC is individually screened for performance potential. The DDR4 form factor
            is optimized for the latest Intel X99 and 100 Series motherboards and offers higher
            frequencies, greater bandwidth, and lower power consumption than DDR3 modules.
            Vengeance LPX DDR4 modules are compatibility-tested across X99 and 100 Series
            motherboards for reliably fast performance. There\'s XMP 2.0 support for trouble-free
            automatic overclocking. And, they\'re available in multiple colors to match your
            motherboard, your components, or just your style.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_3">
        <item>G.Skill Ripjaws V</item>
        <item>$154.94</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB)\n
            - Memory Speed: 3200Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n As the latest addition to the classic Ripjaws family, Ripjaws
            V series is the newest dual-channel DDR4 memory designed for maximum
            compatibility and cutting-edge performance with the 6th generation Intel®
            Core™ processor on the Z170 series chipset. Built with the finest components,
            tested under the most rigorous conditions, and offered in five color options,
            Ripjaws V is the perfect choice for building a new performance system or for a
            simple memory upgrade. Available in a wide range of frequency options from standard
            DDR4-2133MHz to a blistering DDR4-3733MHz in dual channels, Ripjaws V lets you enjoy a
            faster computing experience for gaming, video &amp; image editing, rendering, and data
            processing. Each and every Ripjaws V DDR4 memory kit is tested with G.SKILL\'s rigorous
            validation process on all major performance motherboard brands to ensure the
            best-in-class reliability and compatibility across the widest selection of
            motherboards.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_4">
        <item>PNY XLR8 Desktop Gaming</item>
        <item>$90.85</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 8GB (1 x 8GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 2666Mhz \n\n</item>
        <item>\n PNY\'s premium XLR8 memory features our most aggressive speeds,
            highest bandwidth, lowest latency and power consumption, and most advanced
            thermal performance for maximum PC stability and responsiveness during
            memory-intensive gaming and application use. PNY XLR8 DDR4 memory modules
            are rigorously engineered and tested to ensure peak performance in even the
            most challenging gaming environments. \n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_5">
        <item>HyperX Predator DDR4</item>
        <item>$212.00</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 3000Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n At elite levels of gaming, the margins between hunter and hunted are measured
            in milliseconds, and powerful HyperX® Predator DDR4 can provide the boost that keeps
            you atop the food chain1. Predator DDR4 comes decked out with a menacing black heat
            spreader that will put fear into the hearts of your prey while running cool and
            reliably. Furious speeds up to 4000MHz and CL12-CL19 timings will push those polygons,
            deliver buttery-smooth streaming for your fans, and blaze through your highlight reel
            editing. It\'s available in single module capacities of 8GB-16GB and kits of 2, 4, and
            8 with capacities of 8GB-128GB. The Intel XMP-ready profiles are optimized for Intel\'s
            latest chipsets - just select the profile and you\'re ready to dominate. Dependable
            Predator DDR4 is 100-percent factory-tested at speed, complements both the newest AMD
            and Intel platforms, and comes with a lifetime warranty, so you\'ll have extreme
            performance and leave the worrying to whoever\'s about to try and take
            you on. \n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_6">
        <item>G.SKILL Ripjaws 4 Series 16GB</item>
        <item>$148.35</item>
        <item>4.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 2400Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n G.SKILL Ripjaws 4 series performance DDR4 memory is designed for the
            ultimate experience on the latest Intel X99 platform! Whether you are processing
            large amounts of data or intense gaming, experience smooth system performance with
            the newest next-generation PC memory technology! All Ripjaws 4 memory kits are
            tested with G.SKILL\'s extensive suite of testing software to ensure maximum performance
            and stability. Make Ripjaws 4 the ideal choice for your DDR4 system! Ripjaws 4 series
            DDR4 memory are validated for compatibility with most X99 motherboards under a series
            of rigorous tests in quad channel memory operations. It\'s guaranteed to provide the
            best-in-class performance, compatibility, and stability with the widest range of X99
            motherboards.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_7">
        <item>HyperX FURY 16GB Kit</item>
        <item>$168.99</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 3200Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n HyperX HX432C16FB3K2/16 is a kit of two 1G x 64-bit (8GB) DDR4-3200 CL16 SDRAM
            (Synchronous DRAM) 1Rx8, memory module, based on eight 1G x 8-bit FBGA components per
            module. Each module kit supports Intel® Extreme Memory Profiles (Intel® XMP) 2.0.
            Total kit capacity is 16GB. Each module has been tested to run at DDR4-3200 at a low
            latency timing of 16-18-18 at 1.35V. The SPDs are programmed to JEDEC standard latency
            DDR4-2400 timing of 17-17-17 at 1.2V. Each 288-pin DIMM uses gold contact
            fingers.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_8">
        <item>Crucial 16GB Kit</item>
        <item>$132.25</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (1 x 16GB) \n
            - Memory Speed: 2666Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n In the ever-changing world of technology, any component more than five years
            old is usually in need of an update. At seven years old and counting, that\'s where
            DDR3 memory is at: laptops can only do so much with it. Since the introduction of
            DDR3 memory technology in 2007, processors have doubled in capability, SSDs have
            revolutionized throughput, and graphics cards have drastically increased frame rates,
            leaving memory as a limiting factor. With Crucial DDR4 SODIMMs, crush the DDR3 memory
            bottleneck and unlock a new standard of performance.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_9">
        <item>Corsair Vengeance Pro 16GB</item>
        <item>$199.00</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB)\n
            - Memory Speed: 2666Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n VENGEANCE RGB PRO Series DDR4 overclocked memory lights up your PC
            with mesmerizing dynamic multi-zone RGB lighting, while delivering the best in
            DDR4 performance. Powerful CORSAIR iCUE software brings your system to life with
            dynamic RGB lighting control, synchronized across all your iCUE compatible products,
            including memory, fans, RGB LED light strips, keyboards, mice and more. Customize
            dozens of preset lighting profiles, experiment with a huge variety of user adjustable
            colors and adjust LED brightness to perfectly match your system. Optimized for peak
            performance on the latest Intel and AMD DDR4 motherboards. \n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ram_10">
        <item>Corsair Dominator Platinum 16GB</item>
        <item>$348.99</item>
        <item>5.0</item>
        <item>\n - Memory Type: DDR4\n
            - Memory Capacity: 16GB (2 x 8GB)\n
            - Memory Speed: 3600Mhz\n\n</item>
        <item>\n Corsair Dominator® Platinum RGB DDR4 Memory redefines premium DDR4 memory,
            with superior aluminum craftsmanship, tightly screened high-frequency memory chips
            and 12 ultra-bright, individually addressable Capellix RGB LEDs. Corsair Dominator
            has long been the face of premium, high-performance memory. That heritage and experience
            has led to this: the most advanced DDR4 memory we\'ve ever created. Dominator Platinum
            RGB is available in high-performance speeds of up to 4,800MHz - making it the world\'s
            fastest air-cooled production memory - with generous overclocking headroom to push
            performance even higher.\n\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>